{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "43 + 46",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 33",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 98",
      "answer": 175
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 29",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 39",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 64",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 8",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 45",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 33",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 31",
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 90",
      "answer": 176
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 37",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 22",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 10",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 85",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 14",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 49",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 81",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 66",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 91",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 24",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 59",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 70",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 63",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 96",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 41",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 78",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 72",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 42",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 37",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 75",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 88",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 7",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 7",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 50",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 85",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 9",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 86",
      "answer": 185,
      "test": {
        "q": "What is the capital city of Germany?",
        "a": "???"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 92",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 75",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 64",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 82",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 96",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 56",
      "answer": 146
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 5",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 63",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 55",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 30",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 20",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 40",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 79",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 3",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 55",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 82",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 27",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 73",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 42",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 90",
      "answer": 168
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 59",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 89",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 89",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 33",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 30",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 21",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 85",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 51",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 61",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 66",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 21",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 27",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 37",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 10",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 59",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 33",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 43",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 73",
      "answer": 173
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 64",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 80",
      "answer": 168
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 73",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 25",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 63",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 84",
      "answer": 183
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 22",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 20",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 13",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 95",
      "answer": 184
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 86",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 80",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 45",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 65",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 21",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 4",
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 37",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 74",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 38",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 21",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 36",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 84",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 63",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 2",
      "answer": 39
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 14,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1300,
      "to": 1400
    }
  }
}